<idea-plugin>
    <id>com.tomljump</id>
    <name>TomlJump</name>
    <vendor url="https://github.com/hongshuo-wang/TomlJump">harrison_wang</vendor>
    <description><![CDATA[
        <p>
            TomlJump 为 TOML 配置与对应的项目文件、源码配置声明提供专注的双向跳转能力。
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>从 TOML 字符串文件路径跳转到项目文件。</li>
            <li>在 TOML table、key 与匹配的源码配置声明之间双向跳转。</li>
            <li>支持 Go、Python、Java、TypeScript、JavaScript 中的保守配置匹配。</li>
            <li>使用 JetBrains 原生跳转能力，例如 Go to Declaration 和 command/control click。</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            TomlJump 不替代 TOML 语法高亮、格式化、schema 校验或补全。它只专注于高置信度导航；
            当配置关系不够可信时会静默跳过。
        </p>
        <hr/>
        <p>
            TomlJump adds focused bidirectional navigation between TOML configuration, project files,
            and matching source configuration declarations.
        </p>
        <ul>
            <li>Jump from TOML string file paths to project files.</li>
            <li>Navigate both ways between TOML tables and keys and matching source declarations.</li>
            <li>Resolve conservative config declarations in Go, Python, Java, TypeScript, and JavaScript.</li>
            <li>Use standard JetBrains navigation actions such as Go to Declaration and command/control click.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>
            TomlJump intentionally does not replace TOML syntax highlighting, formatting, schema validation,
            or completion. It focuses on high-confidence navigation and stays quiet when a configuration
            relationship is not credible.
        </p>
    ]]></description>
    <change-notes><![CDATA[
        <ul>
            <li>新增源码到 TOML 的反向导航，支持从 Go、Python、Java、TypeScript 和 JavaScript 配置容器及字段跳转到匹配的 TOML table 和 key。</li>
            <li>唯一可信目标直接打开；多个可信目标使用 JetBrains 原生选择器，并显示完整 TOML 路径和来源文件。</li>
            <li>加强基于所属配置容器的保守匹配，过滤局部变量、嵌套属性、注释和字符串中的伪声明；关系不明确时保持静默。</li>
        </ul>
        <hr/>
        <ul>
            <li>Added source-to-TOML navigation from configuration containers and fields in Go, Python, Java, TypeScript, and JavaScript to matching TOML tables and keys.</li>
            <li>Unique high-confidence targets open directly; multiple credible targets use the native JetBrains chooser with full TOML paths and source file locations.</li>
            <li>Strengthened conservative, owner-aware matching to reject false declarations in local variables, nested properties, comments, and strings while staying quiet for uncertain relationships.</li>
        </ul>
    ]]></change-notes>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
    <depends>org.toml.lang</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <psi.referenceContributor implementation="com.tomljump.jetbrains.TomlJumpReferenceContributor"/>
        <psi.referenceContributor implementation="com.tomljump.jetbrains.config.TomlConfigReferenceContributor"/>
        <gotoDeclarationHandler
            implementation="com.tomljump.jetbrains.config.reverse.SourceToTomlGotoDeclarationHandler"
            order="last"/>
    </extensions>
</idea-plugin>
